<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".activities.PrivacyPolicyActivity">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="0dp">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_margin="20dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="80dp"
                android:text="TrioTech built the DocCam app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by TrioTech at no cost and is intended for use as is.\n\n This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.\n\n If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. \n\n The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at DocCam unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n\n\n Information Collection and Use\n\n For a better experience, while using our Service, we DO NOT COLLECT any personally identifiable information.\n\n The app does use Google Play Services that may collect information used to identify you. Please view the Google Play Services privacy policy for more information. \n\n Google Play Services: https://policies.google.com/terms\n\n\n Log Data\n\n We do not log your data. Your data stays on your device. In the event you decide to share your video, the app you share it to may collect data based on their policies. However, we are not associated with them and do not log your data.\n\n\n Service Providers\n\n We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\n\n ·         To facilitate our Service;\n\n ·         To provide the Service on our behalf;\n\n ·         To perform Service-related services; or\n\n ·         To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\n\n   We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties may have access to your information.\n\n\n Security\n\n We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we do not store any data on our servers or systems. Everything is on your device. Note that external services used by you are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these services. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services\n\n\n Links to Other Sites\n\n This Service may contain links to other sites to credit them for their icons. If you go to a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n\n\n Children’s Privacy\n\n These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.\n\n\n Changes to This Privacy Policy\n\n We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n\n This policy is effective as of 2021-01-06\n\n\n Contact Us\n\n If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at triotechuw@gmail.com.\n\n This privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and modified/generated by App Privacy Policy Generator: https://app-privacy-policy-generator.nisrulz.com/ "></TextView>

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>